question_data = [
    {
        "category":"Entertainment: Video Games",
        "type":"boolean",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "question":"The Indie Game Development Studio Cing, developers of Hotel Dusk and Last Window, went bankrupt on March 1st, 2010.",
        "correct_answer":"True",
        "incorrect_answers":["False"]
    },
    {"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"&quot;Undertale&quot; is an RPG created by Toby Fox and released in 2015.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"There are 6 legendary cards in &quot;Clash Royale&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Donkey Kong was originally set to be a Popeye arcade game.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Pac-Man was invented by the designer Toru Iwatani while he was eating pizza.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In &quot;Super Mario Bros.&quot;, the clouds and bushes have the same artwork and are just different colors.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In &quot;Sonic Adventure&quot;, you are able to transform into Super Sonic at will after completing the main story.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Solid Snake is actually a clone from the DNA of Big Boss in the Metal Gear Solid series&#039; history.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Deus Ex (2000) does not feature the World Trade Center because it was destroyed by terrorist attacks according to the game&#039;s plot.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The main playable character of the 2015 RPG &quot;Undertale&quot; is a monster.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Rebecca Chambers does not appear in any Resident Evil except for the original Resident Evil and the Gamecube remake.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In the game &quot;Subnautica&quot;, a &quot;Spadefish&quot; will attack you.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In Terraria, you can craft the Cell Phone pre-hardmode.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In &quot;Undertale&quot;, the main character of the game is Sans.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In Pok&eacute;mon, Arbok evolves into Seviper.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In RuneScape, one must complete the &quot;Dragon Slayer&quot; quest before equipping Rune Platelegs.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"&quot;Sonic the Hedgehog 2&quot; originally was going to have a time travel system.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In Until Dawn, both characters Sam and Mike cannot be killed under any means until the final chapter of the game.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"There are 2 player roles in Trouble in Terrorist Town.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In the video game &quot;Splatoon&quot;, the playable characters were originally going to be rabbits instead of squids.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Each piece in Tetris is called a tetris.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The game &quot;Jetpack Joyride&quot; was created by &quot;Redbrick Studios&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"&quot;Resident Evil 7&quot; is the first first-person Resident Evil game.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The shotgun appears in every numbered Resident Evil game.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In &quot;Space Station 13&quot;,  the station has a clown aboard it.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]
                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                 }
]